Finding Aid for Claude Halstead Van Tyne papers, 1885-1930
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Claude Halstead Van Tyne papers 1885-1930
Van Tyne, Claude Halstead, 1869-1930.
86747 Aa 2
Professor of history at University of Michigan; scholar of America's revolutionary era. Correspondence concerning the historical profession, publishing, current events, and personal matters; lecture notes, newspaper clippings concerning personal matters and travels in Europe and India; papers concerning his activities during World War I, particularly with the National Security League.
3.5 linear feet
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection came from Mr. Chester Lawton, Van Tyne’s son-in-law (donor no. 3672 ) in 1965-1966.
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Claude Halstead Van Tyne was born October 16, 1869, at Tecumseh, Michigan, to Lawrence M. and Helen (Rosacrans) Van Tyne. He attended the University of Michigan and received the A.B. degree in 1896. He then studied at Heidelberg, Leipzig and Paris, 1897-1898, and earned the Ph.D. degree at the University of Pennsylvania in 1900. From 1903 to 1930 he taught American history at the University of Michigan and served as head of the department of history after 1911. He was chairman of the Michigan Historical Commission and associate editor of the American Historical Review for extended periods. His publications include: The Loyalists in the American Revolution (1902); Guide to the Archives of the Government of the United States in Washington (with W. G. Leland) (1904); The American Revolution (1905); School History of the United States (with A.C. McLaughlin) (1911); Causes of the War of Independence (1921); India in Ferment (1923); England and America, Rivals in the American Revolution (1927). He also edited, The Letters of Daniel Webster (1902). Professor Van Tyne died in Ann Arbor, March 21, 1930.
The Van Tyne collection includes correspondence concerning the historical profession, publishing, current events, and personal matters; lecture notes, newspaper clippings concerning personal matters and Van Tyne's travels in Europe and India. The papers also include material concerning his activities during World War I, particularly with the National Security League. The papers are organized in two series: Correspondence and Professional and Personal Papers.
Subjects:
The Atlantic Monthly.; Europe--Description and travel.; Historians--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; India--Description and travel.; Longman (Firm); McNaught's monthly.; The Michigan Daily.; National Security League.; The New-York times.; Scholarly publishing--Michigan.; Voyages and travels.; University of Michigan. Dept. of History.; University of Michigan--Faculty.; Van Tyne, Claude Halstead, 1869-1930.; William L. Clements Library.; World War, 1914-1918.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Van Tyne, Claude Halstead, 1869-1930.
Contributors:
Adams, Charles Francis, 1835-1915.; Adams, Ephraim Douglass, 1865-1930.; Adams, Randolph Greenfield, 1892-1951.; Aigler, Ralph William, 1885-1964.; Aiton, Arthur Scott, 1894-1955.; Ames, Herman Vandenburg, 1865-1935.; Andrews, Charles McLean, 1863-1943.; Angell, Alexis C. (Alexis Caswell), 1857-1932.; Angell, James Burrill, 1829-1916.; Angell, James Rowland, 1869-1949.; Avery, Sewell Lee, 1873-1960.; Aydelotte, Frank, 1880-1956.; Babst, Earl D., 1870-1967.; Bakeless, John Edwin, 1894-1978.; Barbour, Levi L. (Levi Lewis), 1840-1925.; Barker, Ernest F. (Ernest Franklin), 1886-1970; Bassett, John Spencer, 1867-1928.; Bates, Henry Moore, 1869-1949.; Beal, Junius E. (Junius Emery), 1860-1942.; Becker, Carl Lotus, 1873-1945.; Bemis, Samuel Flagg, 1891-1973.; Billington, Ray Allen, 1903-1981; Boak, Arthur Edward Romilly, 1888-1962.; Bolton, Herbert Eugene, 1870-1953.; Bourne, Henry Eldridge, 1862-1946.; Brown, Everett Somerville, 1886-1964.; Buck, Solon Justus, 1884-1962.; Buckner, Simon Bolivar, 1823-1914.; Bulkley, Harry C. (Harry Conant), b. 1870.; Burr, George Lincoln, 1857-1938.; Burton, Clarence Monroe, 1853-1932.; Burton, Marion Le Roy, 1874-1925.; Byrd, Richard Evelyn, 1888-1957.; Cajori, Florian, 1859-1930.; Campbell, Caroline Belzora, 1859-1926.; Campbell, Henry M. (Henry Munroe), 1854-1926.; Carroll, Eber Malcolm, 1893-1959.; Carton, Augustus C.; Catlin, George B. (George Byron), 1857-1934.; Channing, Edward, 1856-1931.; Chapman, Charles E. (Charles Edward), 1880-1941.; Chase, Lew Allen, 1879-1957.; Chinard, Gilbert, 1881-1972.; Claxton, Philander Priestley, 1862-1957.; Clements, William L. (William Lawrence), 1861-1934.; Cleveland, Frederick Albert, 1865-1946.; Cody, Hiram Sedgewick.; Cole, Arthur Charles, 1886-1976; Condon, Randall J. (Randall Judson), 1862-1931.; Cook, William W. (William Wilson), 1858-1930.; Corwin, Edward Samuel, 1878-1963.; Crane, Ronald S. (Ronald Salmon), 1886-1967.; Crane, Verner W., 1889-1974; Cross, Arthur Lyon, 1873-1940.; Cross, Wilbur L. (Wilbur Lucius), 1862-1948.; D. Appleton and Company.; Davis, Calvin Olin, 1871-; Deardorff, Neva Ruth, 1887-; Detroit Public Library.; Dodd, William Edward, 1869-1940.; Doubleday, Page, & Company.; Dow, Earle Wilbur, 1868-1946.; Dunbar, Willis Frederick, 1902-1970; Dunham, Arthur, 1893-; Dunning, William Archibald, 1857-1922.; Edmonson, James Bartlett, 1882-1954.; Effinger, John Robert, 1869-1933.; Fairlie, John A. (John Archibald), 1872-1947.; Farrand, Max, 1869-1945.; Farrar, John Chipman, 1896-1974; Faulkner, Harold Underwood, 1890-1968.; Ferris, Woodbridge N., 1853-1928.; Ford, Guy Stanton, 1873-1962.; Ford, Worthington Chauncey, 1858-1941.; Fox, Dixon Ryan, 1887-1945.; Frayer, William Alley.; Frédéricq, Paul, 1850-1920.; Garfield, Harry Augustus, 1863-1942.; Garner, James Wilford, 1871-1938.; Gay, Edwin F. (Edwin Francis), 1867-1946.; Gipson, Lawrence Henry, 1880-1971; Gore, Victor M.; Green, Fred W. (Fred Warren), 1872-1936.; Greene, Evarts Boutell, 1870-1947.; Haigh, Henry A. (Henry Allyn), b. 1854.; Hanchett, Benjamin Sawtell, 1868-1933.; Harris, Thomas L. (Thomas Le Grand), 1863-1941.; Hart, Albert Bushnell, 1854-1943.; Haskins, Charles Homer, 1870-1937.; Hayes, Carlton Joseph Huntley, 1882-1964.; Hill, Arthur, 1847-1909.; Hobbs, William Herbert, 1864-1952.; Hodder, Frank Heywood, 1860-1935.; Holt, Hamilton, 1872-1951.; Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964.; Houghton Mifflin Company.; Hubbard, Lucius L. (Lucius Lee), 1849-1933.; Huber, Gotthelf Carl, 1865-1934.; Hull, Charles Henry, b. 1864.; Hulst, Cornelia Steketee, 1865-1957.; Hutchins, Harry B. (Harry Burns), 1847-1930.; Hyma, Albert, 1893-1978; Jameson, J. Franklin (John Franklin), 1859-1937.; Jastrow, Morris, 1861-1921.; Jenks, William Lee, 1856-1936.; Kelley, Patrick Henry, 1867-1925.; Kelsey, Francis W. (Francis Willey), b. 1858.; King, Clyde Lyndon, 1879-1937.; Knappen, Loyal Edwin, 1854-1930.; Koch, Theodore Wesley, 1871-1941.; Kraus, Edward Henry, 1875-1973; Lane, Robert Porter, 1891-1953.; Langer, William L. (William Leonard), 1896-1977.; Larson, Laurence Marcellus, 1868-1938.; Latane, John Holladay, 1869-1932.; Leland, Frank Bruce.; LeRoy, James A. (James Alfred), 1875-1909.; Little, Clarence C. (Clarence Cook), b. 1888.; Lloyd, Alfred H. (Alfred Henry), 1864-1927.; Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1850-1924.; Longman (Firm); Loud, Edward F.; Loud, George Alvin, 1852-1925.; Lovejoy, P. S., 1884-1942.; Lucas, Henry Stephen, 1889-1961.; McClure, Harry H.; McGregor, Tracy William, 1869-1936.; Mackenzie, William Dexter, 1873-1960.; McLaren, Walter Wallace.; McLaughlin, Andrew Cunningham, 1861-1947.; Macmillan Company.; Malcolm, George A. (George Arthur), 1881-1961.; Meany, Edmond S. (Edmond Stephen), 1862-1935.; Miller, Edwin Lillie, 1868-1934.; Millspaugh, Arthur Chester, 1883-1955.; Moore, Charles, 1855-1942.; More, Paul Elmer, 1864-1937.; Morison, Samuel Eliot, 1887-1976.; Muir, Ramsay, 1872-1941.; Murfin, James Orin, 1875-1940.; Myers, Albert Cook, 1874-1960.; Nearing, Scott, 1883-1983.; Nevins, Allan, 1890-1971.; North, Lucian Gregory, 1850-1925.; Notestein, Wallace, 1878-1969.; Oberholtzer, Ellis Paxson, 1868-1936.; Osborn, Chase S. (Chase Salmon), b. 1860.; Pattengill, Henry Romaine, 1852-1918.; Patterson, John C., 1838-1910.; Paxson, Frederic L. (Frederic Logan), 1877-1948.; Pearson, Karl G.; Pease, Theodore Calvin, 1887-1948.; Pelzer, Louis, 1879-1946.; Perry, Maude Elaine Caldwell, 1873-1963.; Perry, Stuart Hoffman, 1874-1957.; Phillips, Ulrich Bonnell, 1877-1934.; Pierce, Bessie Louise, 1888-1974.; Pollock, James K. (James Kerr), 1898-1968; Potter, William W., 1869-1940.; Pound, Arthur, 1884-1966.; Priestley, Herbert Ingram, 1875-1944.; Putnam, George Haven, 1844-1930.; Putnam, Herbert, 1861-1955.; Rand, Benjamin, 1856-1934.; Randall, J. G. (James Garfield), 1881-1953.; Rankin, Thomas Ernest, 1872-1953.; Rebec, George, 1868-1944.; Reeves, Jesse Siddall, 1872-1942; Riggs, Henry Earle, b. 1865.; Robbins, Frank Egleston, 1884-; Robertson, James Alexander, 1873-1939.; Robinson, Edgar Eugene, 1887-1977; Robinson, James Harvey, 1863-1936.; Rolfe, John Carew, 1859-1943.; Rose, John Holland, 1855-1942.; Ruthven, Alexander Grant, 1882-1971.; Sawyer, Walter H. (Walter Hulme), 1861-1931.; Schelling, Felix Emmanuel, 1858-1945.; Schevill, Ferdinand, 1868-1954.; Schlesinger, Arthur Meier, 1888-1965.; Scribner, Charles, 1854-1930.; Seligman, Edwin Robert Anderson, 1861-1939.; Sellery, George C. (George Clarke), 1872-; Shorts, Robert P. (Robert Perry), 1879-1975; Shotwell, Ambrose Milton, 1853-; Shotwell, James Thomson, 1874-1965.; Siebert, Wilbur Henry, 1866-1961.; Sioussat, St. George L. (St. George Leakin), 1878-1960.; Slosson, Edwin Emery, 1865-1929.; Slosson, Preston W. (Preston William), 1892-1984; Smith, Shirley Wheeler, 1875-1959.; Smith, William Alden, 1859-1932.; Spaulding, Mr. (Oliver Lyman), 1833-1922.; Stephenson, Wendell Holmes, 1899-1970.; Stone, Ralph, 1868-1956.; Sweet, William Warren, 1881-1959.; Swinton, Roy Stanley, 1886-; Tarbell, Ida M. (Ida Minerva), 1857-1944.; Tatlock, John S. P. (John Strong Perry), 1876-1948.; Teggart, Frederick John, 1870-1946.; Thayer, William Roscoe, 1859-1923.; Thompson, James Westfall, 1869-1941.; Thwaites, Reuben Gold, 1853-1913.; Trevelyan, George Macaulay, 1876-1962.; Trevelyan, George Otto, Sir, bart., 1838-1928.; Turner, Edward Raymond, 1881-1929.; Turner, Frederick Jackson, 1861-1932.; Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), 1884-1951.; Vander Velde, Lewis G. (Lewis George), 1890-1975.; Waldo, Dwight Bryant, 1864-1939.; Walker, Williston, 1860-1922.; Weissert, Charles Adam, 1878-1947.; Wenley, R. M. (Robert Mark), 1861-1929.; White, Lee A., b. 1886.; White, William Allen, 1868-1944.; Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924.; Wister, Owen, 1860-1938.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Correspondence 1885-1931 (first accession)
  The Van Tyne correspondence files were received in two separate accessions. The first includes material from 1885 to 1930 while the second spans the years 1901-1931.
  - 1885-1930 (1st accession)
    Most of the correspondents in the first accession were indexed (see the Selective Index to Correspondents section below). The correspondence concerns the historical profession, publishing, current events, and professional matters. Correspondents include other historians, University of Michigan administrators and faculty members, publishers, and other colleagues. Of special interest are letters documenting Van Tyne's reaction to United States policies prior to entry into World War I. Some of the correspondents include Sir George Otto Trevelyan, George M. Trevelyan, Albert Bushnell Hart, John F. Jameson, Andrew Cunningham McLaughlin, Ulrich B. Phillips. And Frederick Jackson Turner.
    - 1885-1923, 24 folders (Box 1)
      (folder nos. 1-24)
    - 1924-1930 undated, 9 folders (Box 2)
      (folder nos. 25-33)
  - 1901-1931 (second accession)
    This second accession of correspondents is only partially indexed. The content of the letters concerns Van Tyne's research, publications, and his relationship with other historians.
    - 1901-1905 (Box 2)
      (folder no. 34)
    - 1906-1910 (Box 2)
      (folder no. 35)
    - 1911-1913 (Box 2)
      (folder no. 36)
    - 1914-1915 (Box 2)
      (folder no. 37)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 2)
      (folder no. 38)
    - January-June 1918 (Box 2)
      (folder no. 39)
    - July-December 1918 (Box 2)
      (folder no. 40)
    - 1919 (Box 2)
      (folder no. 41)
    - 1920 (Box 2)
      (folder no. 42)
    - 1921 (Box 2)
      (folder no. 43)
    - 1922 (Box 2)
      (folder no. 44)
    - 1923 (Box 2)
      (folder no. 45)
    - 1924 (Box 2)
      (folder no. 46)
    - 1925 (Box 2)
      (folder no. 47)
    - 1926 (Box 2)
      (folder no. 48)
    - 1927 (Box 2)
      (folder no. 49)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 3)
      (folder no. 50)
    - Undated (Box 3)
      (folder no. 51)
    - 1912-1920 with Sir George Otto Trevelyan (Box 3)
      (folder no. 52)
    - 1921-1927 with Sir George Otto Trevelyan (Box 3)
      (folder no. 53)
    - 1922-1931 with George M. Trevelyan (Box 3)
      (folder no. 54)
- Professional and Personal Papers
  The Professional and Personal Papers series is noteworthy for Van Tyne's World War I activities, including copies of the lecture on war aims given to the Student Army Training Corps at the University of Michigan.
  - Trip down the Danube River, letters published in the newspaper 1896 (Box 3)
    (folder no. 54-A)
  - Trip to India
    - Correspondence 1921-1922 (Box 3)
      (folder no. 55)
    - Lecture notes concerning India (Box 3)
      (folder no. 56)
    - Newspaper clippings 1921-1922 (Box 3)
      (folder no. 57)
  - University of Michigan History Department and Clements Library 1910-1928 (Box 3)
    (folder no. 58)
  - Lecture notes (Box 3)
    (folder no.59)
  - Lecture notes (Box 3)
    (folder no. 60)
  - World War I era activities and events
    - Newspaper clippings 1917-1918 (Box 3)
      (folder no. 61)
    - National Security League papers 1918 (Box 3)
      (folder no. 62)
    - Newspaper clippings 1914-1918 concerning World War I and Germany (Box 3)
      (folder no. 63)
    - Newspaper clippings 1914-1918 concerning World War I and Germany (Box 3)
      (folder no.64)
  - Newspaper obituaries 1930 (Box 3)
    (folder no. 65)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings (Box 3)
    (folder no. 66)
  - Articles and reviews, 3 folders (Box 3)
    (folder nos. 67-69)
  - Drafts of articles (Box 3)
    (folder no. 70)
  - Mrs. Claude H. Van Tyne papers 1930-1933 (Box 3)
    (folder no. 71)
  - Miscellanea, 5 folders (Box 3)
  - Research Note cards (sample) (Box 3)
  - Photographs: portraits (Box 3)
  - War Aims Lectures taught to Student Army Training Corps at the University of Michigan 1917
    - General Outline (Box 4)
    - First Lecture, Prof. Van Tyne (Box 4)
    - Second Lecture, Prof. Turner (Box 4)
    - Third Lecture, Prof. Frayer (Box 4)
    - Fourth Lecture, Prof. Frayer (Box 4)
    - Fifth Lecture, Prof. Frayer (Box 4)
    - Sixth Lecture, Prof. Frayer (Box 4)
    - Seventh Lecture, Prof. Frayer (Box 4)
    - Eighth Lecture, Prof. Frayer (Box 4)
    - Ninth Lecture, Prof. Frayer (Box 4)
    - Tenth Lecture, Prof. Turner (Box 4)
    - Eleventh Lecture, Prof. Turner (Box 4)
    - Twelfth Lecture, Prof. Turner (Box 4)
    - Thirteenth Lecture, Prof. Turner (Box 4)
    - Fourteenth Lecture, Prof. Turner (Box 4)
    - Fifteenth Lecture, Prof. Turner (Box 4)
    - Sixteenth Lecture, Prof. Turner (Box 4)
    - Seventeenth Lecture, Prof. Turner (Box 4)
    - Eighteenth Lecture, Prof. Turner (Box 4)
    - Nineteenth Lecture, Prof. Frayer (Box 4)
    - Twentieth Lecture, Prof. Frayer (Box 4)
    - Twenty-first Lecture, Prof. Van Tyne (Box 4)
    - Twenty-Second Lecture, Prof. Van Tyne (Box 4)
    - Twenty-Third Lecture, Prof. Van Tyne (Box 4)
    - Twenty-fourth Lecture, Prof. Van Tyne (Box 4)
    - Twenty-fifth Lecture, Prof. Turner (Box 4)
    - Twenty-Sixth Lecture, Prof. Turner (Box 4)
    - Twenty-Seventh Lecture, Prof. Turner (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 4)
Selective Index to Correspondents
Adams, Charles Francis, 1835-1915.
Dec. 24, 1901 to S. S. McClure Company.
Adams, Ephraim Douglass, 1865-1930.
Dec. 9, 1911, Dec. 14, 1911, Apr. 7, 1917, May 25, 1917, Jan. 28, 1924.
Adams, Randolph Greenfield, 1892-1951.
Dec. 11, 1923, July 10, 1924, Oct. 9, 1924, July 1, 1925 (copy of letter addressed to E. C. Pardon, Superintendent of buildings and grounds), July 17, 1925, July 23, 1925, Aug. 10, 1925, Apr. 16, 1926, Oct. 25, 1927 (copy of letter to W. L. Clements), June 6, 1928, May 4, 1929, July 4, 1929.
Aigler, Ralph William, 1885-1964.
Jan. 15, 1918.
Aiton, Arthur Scott, 1894-1955.
Oct. 11, 1928, Feb. 16, 1929.
Ames, Herman Vandenburg, 1865-1935.
Apr. 12, 1903, Jan. 27, 1909, Apr. 27, 1910, Mar. 25, 1922, Apr. 5, 1911, Jan. 17, 1917, Aug. 31, 1918, Dec. 11, 1925, Dec. 13, 1928.
Andrews, Charles McLean, 1863-1943.
May 15, 1910, Apr. 28, 1918, Oct. 3, 1920, Dec. 20, 1920, Aug. 10, 1921, Sept. 27, 1921, May 24, 1922, Oct. 9, 1922, Nov. 22, 1922, Jan. 10, 1923, Mar. 14, 1923, June 1, 1923, June 6, 1925, Nov. 30, 1925, Dec. 12, 1925, Apr. 23, 1926, June 25, 1926, Jan. 11, 1929, Feb. 23, 1929, Mar. 3, 1929.
Angell, Alexis C. (Alexis Caswell), 1857-1932.
Apr. 3, 1919.
Angell, James Burrill, 1829-1916.
Apr. 19, 1904, Oct. 27, 1906, Sept. 25, 1908, June 25, 1906 [folder no. 35]; July 29, 1906 [folder no. 35]
Angell, James Rowland, 1869-1949.
Apr. 14, 1926, (copy of letter to William H. Hobbs).
Avery, Sewell Lee, 1873-1960.
Oct. 31, 1917, Apr. 30, 1925.
Aydelotte, Frank, 1880-1956.
Nov. 18, 1918, Nov. 18, 1918 to Nelson, Joseph Raleigh, Nov. 20, 1918.
Babst, Earl D., 1870-1967.
Jan. 29, 1927
Bakeless, John Edwin, 1894-1978.
Sept. ?, 1921
Barbour, Levi L. (Levi Lewis), 1840-1925.
Feb. 18, 1907.
Barker, Ernest Franklin, 1886-
May 8, 1929.
Bassett, John Spencer, 1867-1928.
June 16, 1910. (American Historical Association) Dec. 13, 1910, June 6, 1923, Sept. 18, 1923, Oct. 27, 1924, Sept. 28, 1923.
Bates, Henry Moore, 1869-1949.
Dec. 30, 1913 (1st page only), Apr. 19, 1927, June 10, 1927 (included with P. Slosson letter of June 12, 1927).
Beal, Junius E. (Junius Emery), 1860-1942.
Dec. 12, 1912, May 23, 1913.
Becker, Carl Lotus, 1873-1945.
Dec. 23, 1911, Aug. 6, 1915, Jan. 1, 1911 [folder no. 36], Jan. 27, 1912 [folder no. 36], Apr. 25, 1912 [folder no. 36]; Aug. 12, 1915 [folder no. 37].
Bemis, Samuel Flagg, 1891-1973.
Oct. 12, 1925.
Billington, Ray Allen, 1903-
Nov. 13, 1927.
Boak, Arthur Edward Romilly, 1888-1962.
July 31, 1918, Aug. 6, 1918, Jan. 22, 1922, Oct. 1, 1924, Jan. 1, 1927, May 25, 1925, Feb. 11, 1927, Feb. 26, 1927, May 15, 1927, May 29, 1927, June 26, 1927, July 22, 1927, Jan. 19, 1930.
Bolton, Herbert Eugene, 1870-1953.
Apr. 13, 1912, May 2, 1912, Mar. 10, 1915, Apr. 16, 1915, May 18, 1915, June 7, 1915, Jan. 24, 1916, Dec. 7, 1925.
Bourne, Henry Eldridge, 1862-1946.
Feb. 5, 1930 to Mrs. Claude Halstead Van Tyne.
Brown, Everett Somerville, 1886-1964.
Sept. 27, 1920, Oct. 22, 1920, Jan. 11, 1921.
Buck, Solon Justus, 1884-1962.
Apr. 6, 1910.
Buckner, Simon Bolivar, 1823-1914.
June 10, 1861 to Mogoffin, Beriah, the governor of Kentucky.
Bulkley, Harry C. (Harry Conant), b. 1870.
June 6, 1912.
Burr, George Lincoln, 1857-1938.
July 20, 1911.
Burton, Clarence Monroe, 1853-1932.
Dec. 3, 1910, Oct. 12, 1921, Oct. 26, 1921 to Gray, Paul H., Nov. 4, 1921, Nov. 7, 1921 copies of three letters, Feb. 16, 1922, July 8, 1922, Apr. 18, 1925 to Fuller, George Newman, 1873-1957, Oct. 22, 1928.
Burton, Marion Le Roy, 1874-1925.
Mar. 24, 1919, Nov. 16, 1920, Dec. 15, 1920, Oct. 24, 1921, Oct. 29, 1921, Nov. 21, 1921, Feb. 28, 1922, Sept. 8, 1922, Dec. 1, 1923, Dec. 7, 1923, Feb. 6, 1924, Feb. 15, 1924, Mar. 18, 1924, Apr. 1, 1924.
Byrd, Richard Evelyn, 1888-1957.
Sept. 6, 1926, Oct. 2, 1926, Oct. 8, 1926, Nov. 4, 1927.
Cajori, Florian, 1859-1930.
Oct. 12, 1911.
Campbell, Caroline Belzora, 1859-1926.
Nov. 27, 1916.
Campbell, Henry M. (Henry Munroe), 1854-1926.
Nov. 3, 1921 to Burton, Clarence Monroe.
Carroll, Eber Malcolm, 1893-1959.
Jan. 21, 1918, July 21, 1923, Oct. 1, 1923, Nov. 12, 1923, Dec. 12, 1924, Oct. 20, 1925.
Carton, Augustus C.
Sept. 25, 1918, Dec. 8, 1922, Oct. 23, 1928.
Catlin, George B. (George Byron), 1857-1934.
Feb. 29, 1916
Channing, Edward, 1856-1931.
Oct. 13, 1911, Mar. 8, 1922
Chapman, Charles E. (Charles Edward), 1880-1941.
June 2, 1925, Apr. 11, 1927
Chase, Lew Allen, 1879-1957.
Sept. 13, 1908, Oct. 24, 1908, Nov. 9, 1908, Mar. 14, 1910, Mar. 21, 1910, Apr. 13, 1910, Oct. 1, 1911, Feb. 2, 1912, Mar. 18, 1912, Apr. 26, 1912, June 23, 1916, June 28, 1917, Feb. 9, 1918, July 23, 1918, Sept. 22, 1918, Sept. 26, 1918
July 11, 1922, Feb. 6, 1923, June 15, 1923, Nov. 18, 1923, Dec. 20, 1923, Jan. 26, 1924, May 19, 1925, July 23, 1925, Oct. 27, 1925, Nov. 1, 1925, Nov. 8, 1925, Nov. 10, 1925, Nov. 24, 1925, Dec. 1, 1925, Dec. 5, 1925, June 24, 1926, Sept. 3, 1926, May 3, 1927, Sept. 16, 1928, Nov. 24, 1928, Jan. 2, 1929, Jan. 10, 1929, Jan. 29, 1929.
Chinard, Gilbert, 1881-1972.
Apr. 25, 1925.
Claxton, Philander Priestley, 1862-1957.
June 19, 1918.
Clements, William L. (William Lawrence), 1861-1934.
Feb. 15, 1909, Dec. 11, 1914, May 24, 1915, Aug. 27, 1915, Oct. 26, 1915, Dec. 6, 1915, Jan. 26, 1916, Feb. 2, 1916, Feb. 4, 1916, Feb. 16, 1916, Apr. 18, 1916, July 24, 1916, Jan. 17, 1917, May 16, 1917, Sept. 22, 1917, Oct. 10, 1917, Aug. 9, 1918, Aug. 14, 1919, Nov. 1, 1919, Dec. 1, 1919
June 4, 1920, Aug. 11, 1920, Apr. 26, 1921, Nov. 11, 1921, (Minutes), June 13, 1922, July 22, 1922, Sept. 19, 1922, Nov. 1, 1922, Feb. 9, 1923, Oct. 30, 1923, Nov. 3, 1923, Nov. 8, 1924, Nov. 11, 1924, Dec. 23, 1924, Mar. 18, 1925, May 19, 1925, Aug. 11, 1925, Dec. 5, 1925, Dec. 10, 1925, July 5, 1928, Apr. 8, 1929, May 4, 1929, June 4, 1929, Oct. 17, 1929, Nov. 11, 1929, Nov. 18, 1929, Dec. 12, 1929.
Cleveland, Frederick Albert, 1865-1946.
Mr. 25, 1903, May 21, 1920, Oct. 21, 1913, Oct. 12, 1912.
Cody, Hiram Sedgewick.
Sept, 24, 1908.
Cole, Arthur Charles, 1886-
May 14, 1910, Nov. 22, 1910, May 8, 1911, Feb. 18, 1912, Mar. 1, 1912, Apr. 20, 1912, Aug. 27, 1913, Feb. 16, 1925.
Condon, Randall J. (Randall Judson), 1862-1931.
Mar. 30, 1918.
Cook, William W. (William Wilson), 1858-1930.
June 5, 1929, Nov. 15, 1929.
Corwin, Edward Samuel, 1878-1963.
Nov. 13, 1904, Mar. 2, 1905, May 28, 1905, May 6, 1906, Feb. 5, 1907, Nov. 25, 1908, Nov. 16, 1909, May 6, 1910, May 13, 1910.
Crane, Ronald S. (Ronald Salmon), 1886-1967.
May 1, 1911.
Crane, Verner Winslow, 1889-
Sept. 12, 1911, Dec. 20, 1911, Jan. 21, 1912, Nov. 27, 1914, May 6, 1922, Dec. 31, 1923, May 27, 1925.
Cross, Arthur Lyon, 1873-1940.
Apr. 11, 1910, July 14, 1912, July 27, 1913, Oct. 19, 1913, Apr. 19, 1914, Apr. 26, 1918, May 5, 1918, July 25, 1924, Aug. 26, 1925.
Cross, Wilbur L. (Wilbur Lucius), 1862-1948.
Jan. 20, 1925, Mar. 2, 1925.
Davis, Calvin Olin, 1871-
Feb. 25, 1905.
Deardorff, Neva Ruth, 1887-
Apr. 26, 1911, Jan. 7, 1912.
Dodd, William Edward, 1869-1940.
Mar. 8, 1909, Nov. 29, 1909, Jan. 13, 1913, May 21, 1925, Nov. 15, 1925.
Dow, Earle Wilbur, 1868-1946.
Sept. 15, 1911, Jan. 26, 1914, July 9, 1914, Sept. 11, 1919, Sept. 7, 1926.
Dunbar, Willis Frederick, 1902-
Dec. 31, 1928.
Dunham, Arthur, 1893-
June 12, 1923.
Dunning, William Archibald, 1857-1922.
Jan. 21, 1907, Mar. 9, 1911, Mar. 14, 1911.
Edmonson, James Bartlett, 1882-1954.
Feb. 14, 1929, Feb. 23, 1929, Feb. 28, 1929.
Effinger, John Robert, 1869-1933.
Nov. 13, 1911, Jan. 5, 1914, Feb. 16, 1916, June 4, 1926, Jan. 18, 1929, June 5, 1929, Dec. 26, 1929.
Fairlie, John A. (John Archibald), 1872-1947.
May 20, 1907, Apr. 26, 1908, Feb. 13, 1910.
Farrand, Max, 1869-1945.
Nov. 24, -, July 31, 1911, Jan. 22, 1912, Mar. 15, 1914, Mar. 27, 1914.
Farrar, John Chipman, 1896-
Dec. 7, 1928.
Faulkner, Harold Underwood, 1890-1968.
Mar. 8, 1926.
Ferris, Woodbridge N., 1853-1928.
May 16, 1913, Sept. 25, 1916.
Ford, Guy Stanton, 1873-1962.
Mar. 3, 1926.
Ford, Worthington Chauncey, 1858-1941.